schoolsfirstfcu.org 2012-10-16

# FACTS

                                                                                                       Rev. 07/2012
                      WHAT DOES SCHOOLSFIRST FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
     FACTS            DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                      gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
                      us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please
                      read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
                      service you have with us. This information can include:
                              Social Security number and Income
                              Payment history and transaction history
                              Account balances and credit card or other debt
                      When you are no longer our Member, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
How?                  All financial companies need to share customersʼ personal information to run their
                      everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                      share their customersʼ personal information; the reasons SchoolsFirst FCU chooses to
                      share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                         Does SchoolsFirst FCU      Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                         share?                     sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                   Yes                            No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                   Yes                            No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial
                                                                    No                       We donʼt share
companies
For our affiliatesʼ everyday business purposes—
                                                                    No                       We donʼt share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliatesʼ everyday business purposes—
                                                                    No                       We donʼt share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                  No                       We donʼt share
Questions?                     Call 800.462.8328 or go to schoolsfirstfcu.org

Page 2
What we do
How does SchoolsFirst FCU        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information? and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                 These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                 and buildings.
How does SchoolsFirst FCU        We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?          open an account or apply for a loan
                                          pay your bills or deposit money
                                          use your credit or debit card
                                 We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                 credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                          sharing for affiliatesʼ everyday business purposes—
                                           information about your creditworthiness
                                          affiliatesʼ from using your information to market to you
                                          sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                 State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights
                                 to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                 financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          SchoolsFirst FCU has no affiliates for purposes of privacy
                                           and information sharing.
Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                 be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          SchoolsFirst FCU does not share with nonaffiliates so they
                                           can market to you.
Joint marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                 together market financial products or services to you.
                                          SchoolsFirst FCU doesnʼt jointly market.
